Laderrick Jackson

Surgical Tech

Dallas, TX ljackson0202@yahoo.com 6015437519

Hardworking, motivated professional and U.S. Army veteran that has extensive knowledge of surgical instrumentation and operating room procedures. Possesses excellent preparation listening and communication skills. I am a highly motivated person

with more than 5 years of experience and achievements, including training as an Operating Room Specialist, patient administration, Vascular team surgical tech and Sterile Processing Manager. I actively seeks

additional responsibilities and resolves problems quickly and efficiently. My achievements allowed me to earn leadership positions, provide assistance to medical staff, patients and healthcare procedures.

Willing to relocate: Anywhere

Authorized to work in the US for any employer

Work Experience

Vascular Surgical Tech

Forrest General Hospital - Hattiesburg, MS February 2017 to March 2018

who cares and assist surgery for patients with diseases that affect the arteries, veins, and lymphatic systems exclusive of the heart and intracranial (within the brain) circulations. Hardening of the arteries or atherosclerosis is a common cause of vascular disease. Performed general Diagnostic radiological procedures and operate all Diagnostic radiological equipment. Ensure all paperwork and computer entries adequately completed and work given to radiologists for interpretation.

Operating Room Specialist/ Surgical tech

United States Army - Fort Campbell, KY September 2013 to November 2016

In my two in a half years of being a surgical tech Ive assists the nursing staff in preparing the patient and the operating room

environment for surgery and for providing assistance to the medical staff during surgical procedures. Ive also operate the centralized material service (CMS). Im responsible for preparing and maintaining sterile medical supplies and special

equipment for medical treatment facilities. As a surgical tech we assists in the management of the operating room suites.

Assists in preparing patients and operating room environment for surgery and provides assistance to the medical staff during surgical procedures to include the creation and maintenance of sterile fields for surgical procedures, the draping of patients, the

preparation, manipulation, and delivery of basic surgical instruments and equipment, and the accountability for all instruments,

needles, sponges and medications placed within the sterile field. I performs various preoperative and postoperative procedures as directed and maintain the cleanliness of the operating room. Receives, cleans, decontaminates, sterilizes, stores and issues

various medical supplies and equipment used during surgical procedures. Responsible for the sterilization process, which includes inspecting, cleaning, assembling, warping and sterilizing equipment. Operates and runs sterilization checks on a variety of sterilization equipment to include Steam, ETO, Sterrad and Steris Systems. Understand the individual's needs, work with nurses and medical staff at facility to make sure they are prepared for the person with all vital information. Ability to keep organized and accurate records.

Education

Associate in Science

Pearl River Community College - Hattiesburg, MS August 2016 to May 2018

U.S Army Operating Room Specialist Training - Fort Sam Houston, TX 2013 to 2014

real estate salesman course in real estate

MREC real estate school - Hattiesburg, MS

Skills

Photography (3 years), Surgical Technologist, CST, Surgical Tech, Sterile Processing, Operating Room

Military Service

Branch: Army

Service Country: United States

Rank: Specialist

June 2013 to November 2016

Certifications/Licenses

CPR/BLS

Surgical Technologist

Additional Information

Skills

Operating Room Specialist Course Quick learner completed all Window server 2003 courses Team leader Combat lifesaver Course Adept multi-tasker Structured Self Development course Critical thinking Field Sanitation Team BLS certified Basic Combat Training First Aid certified patient administration course Lead tech in General surgery